Guide to the Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143 1872-1976
Archives Union File Part 2, Section 3: Boxes 130-143
- TWU Express, 1957; Publication (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1957; Publication (Box 134, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.1 (1957: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1957; Publication (Box 134, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.2 (1957: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1957; Publication (Box 134, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.3 (1957: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1957; Publication (Box 134, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.4 (1957: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1957; Publication (Box 134, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.5 (1957: May)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1957; Publication (Box 134, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.6 (1957: June)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1957; Publication (Box 134, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.7 (1957: July)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1957; Publication (Box 134, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.8 (1957: Aug.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1957; Publication (Box 134, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.9 (1957: Sept.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1957; Publication (Box 134, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.10 (1957: Oct.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1957; Publication (Box 134, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.11 (1957: Nov.)
  - Item 12: TWU Express, 1957; Publication (Box 134, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.9:no.12 (1957: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1958; Publication (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1958; Publication (Box 134, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.1 (1958: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1958; Publication (Box 134, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.2 (1958: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1958; Publication (Box 134, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.3 (1958: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1958; Publication (Box 134, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.4 (1958: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1958; Publication (Box 134, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.5 (1958: May)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1958; Publication (Box 134, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.6 (1958: June-July)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1958; Publication (Box 134, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.7 (1958: Aug.)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1958; Publication (Box 134, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.8 (1958: Sept.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1958; Publication (Box 134, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.9 (1958: Oct.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1958; Publication (Box 134, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.10 (1958: Nov.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1958; Publication (Box 134, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.11 (1958: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1959; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1959; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.11:no.1 (1959: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1959; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.11:no.2 (1959: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1959; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.11:no.3 (1959: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1959; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.11:no.4 (1959: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1959; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.11:no.5 (1959: May)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1959; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.11:no.6 (1959: June)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1959; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.11:no.7 (1959: July)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1959; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.11:no.8 (1959: Aug.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1959; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.11:no.9 (1959: Sept.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1959; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.11:no.10 (1959: Oct.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1959; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.11:no.11 (1959: Nov.)
  - Item 12: TWU Express, 1959; Publication (Box 134, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.11:no.12 (1959: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1960; Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1960; Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.1 (1960: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1960; Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.2 (1960: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1960; Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.3 (1960: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1960; Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.4 (1960: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1960; Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.5 (1960: May)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1960; Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.6 (1960: June)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1960; Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.7 (1960: July)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1960; Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.8 (1960: Aug.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1960; Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.9 (1960: Sept.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1960; Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.10 (1960: Oct.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1960; Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.11 (1960: Nov.)
  - Item 12: TWU Express, 1960; Publication (Box 135, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.12:no.12 (1960: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1961; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1961; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.1 (1961: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1961; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.2 (1961: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1961; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.3 (1961: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1961; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.4 (1961: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1961; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.5 (1961: May)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1961; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.6 (1961: June)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1961; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.7 (1961: July)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1961; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.8 (1961: Aug.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1961; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.9 (1961: Sept.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1961; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.10 (1961: Oct.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1961; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.11 (1961: Nov.)
  - Item 12: TWU Express, 1961; Publication (Box 135, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.13:no.12 (1961: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1962; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1962; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.1 (1962: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1962; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.2 (1962: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1962; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.3 (1962: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1962; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.4 (1962: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1962; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.5 (1962: May)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1962; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.6 (1962: June)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1962; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.7 (1962: July)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1962; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.8 (1962: Aug.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1962; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.9 (1962: Sept.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1962; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.10 (1962: Oct.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1962; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.11 (1962: Nov.)
  - Item 12: TWU Express, 1962; Publication (Box 135, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.14:no.12 (1962: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.15:no.1 (1963: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.15:no.2 (1963: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.15:no.3 (1963: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.15:no.4 (1963: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.15:no.5 (1963: May)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.15:no.6 (1963: June)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.15:no.7 (1963: July)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.15:no.8 (1963: Aug.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.15:no.9 (1963: Sept.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.15:no.10 (1963: Oct.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.15:no.11 (1963: Nov.)
  - Item 12: TWU Express, 1963; Publication (Box 135, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.15:no.12 (1963: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1964; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1964; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.2 (1964: Feb.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1964; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.3 (1964: Mar.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1964; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.4 (1964: Apr.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1964; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.5 (1964: May)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1964; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.6 (1964: June)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1964; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.7 (1964: July)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1964; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.8 (1964: Aug.)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1964; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.9 (1964: Sept.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1964; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.10 (1964: Oct.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1964; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.11 (1964: Nov.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1964; Publication (Box 136, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.16:no.12 (1964: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1965; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1965; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.1 (1965: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1965; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.2 (1965: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1965; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.3 (1965: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1965; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.4 (1965: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1965; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.5 (1965: May)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1965; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.6 (1965: June)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1965; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.7 (1965: July)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1965; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.8 (1965: Aug.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1965; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.9 (1965: Sept.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1965; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.10 (1965: Oct.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1965; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.11 (1965: Nov.)
  - Item 12: TWU Express, 1965; Publication (Box 136, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no.12 (1965: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1966; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1966; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.1 (1966: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1966; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.2 (1966: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1966; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.3 (1966: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1966; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.4 (1966: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1966; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.5 (1966: May)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1966; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.6 (1966: June)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1966; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.7 (1966: July)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1966; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.8 (1966: Aug.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1966; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.9 (1966: Sept.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1966; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.10 (1966: Oct.)
  - Item 11: TWU Express, 1966; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.11 (1966: Nov.)
  - Item 12: TWU Express, 1966; Publication (Box 136, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.18:no.12 (1966: Dec.)
- TWU Express, 1969; Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: TWU Express, 1969; Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.21:no.1 (1969: Jan.)
  - Item 2: TWU Express, 1969; Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.21:no.2 (1969: Feb.)
  - Item 3: TWU Express, 1969; Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.21:no.3 (1969: Mar.)
  - Item 4: TWU Express, 1969; Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.21:no.4 (1969: Apr.)
  - Item 5: TWU Express, 1969; Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.21:no.6 (1969: June)
  - Item 6: TWU Express, 1969; Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.21:no.7 (1969: July)
  - Item 7: TWU Express, 1969; Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.21:no.8 (1969: Aug.)
  - Item 8: TWU Express, 1969; Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.21:no.9 (1969: Sept.)
  - Item 9: TWU Express, 1969; Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.21:no.10 (1969: Oct.)
  - Item 10: TWU Express, 1969; Publication (Box 136, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.21:no.12 (1969: Dec.)
- UAW Solidarity, 1957-1958 (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: UAW Solidarity, 1957; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Author: International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft and Agricultural Implement Workers of America
    Notes: v.1:no.1 (1957: Dec. 16). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 2: UAW Solidarity, 1957; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.2 (1957: Dec. 23). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 3: UAW Solidarity, 1957; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.3 (1957: Dec. 30). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 4: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.7 (1958: Jan. 27). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 5: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.8 (1958: Feb. 3). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 6: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.9 (1958: Feb. 10). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 7: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.10 (1958: Feb. 17). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 8: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.14 (1958: Mar. 17). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 9: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.15 (1958: Mar. 24). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 10: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.16 (1958: Mar. 31). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 11: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.19 (1958: Apr. 21). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 12: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.20 (1958: Apr. 27). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 13: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.21 (1958: May 5). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 14: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.22 (1958: May 19). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 15: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.23 (1958: June 2). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 16: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.24 (1958: June 16). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 17: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.25 (1958: June 30). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 18: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.26 (1958: July 14). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 19: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.27 (1958: July 28). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 20: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.28 (1958: Aug. 11). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 21: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.29 (1958: Aug. 25). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 22: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.30 (1958: Sept. 8). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 23: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.31 (1958: Sept. 22). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 24: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.32 (1958: Oct. 6). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 25: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.33 (1958: Oct. 27). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 26: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.34 (1958: Nov. 10). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 27: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.35 (1958: Nov. 24). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 28: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.36 (1958: Dec. 8). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 29: UAW Solidarity, 1958; Publication (Box 137, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.1:no.37 (1958: Dec. 22). Eastern Edition.
- UAW Solidarity, 1959-1960 (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: UAW Solidarity, 1959; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1959: Jan. 19). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 2: UAW Solidarity, 1959; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.2 (1959: Feb. 16). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 3: UAW Solidarity, 1959; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.3 (1959: Mar. 16). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 4: UAW Solidarity, 1959; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.4 (1959: Apr.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 5: UAW Solidarity, 1959; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1959: June). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 6: UAW Solidarity, 1959; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.6 (1959: July). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 7: UAW Solidarity, 1959; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.8 (1959: Aug.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 8: UAW Solidarity, 1959; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.9 (1959: Sept.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 9: UAW Solidarity, 1959; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.10 (1959: Oct.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 10: UAW Solidarity, 1959; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.2:no.12 (1959: Dec.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 11: UAW Solidarity, 1960; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.2 (1960: Feb.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 12: UAW Solidarity, 1960; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.3 (1960: Mar.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 13: UAW Solidarity, 1960; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.5 (1960: May). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 14: UAW Solidarity, 1960; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.6 (1960: June). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 15: UAW Solidarity, 1960; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.9 (1960: Aug. 15). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 16: UAW Solidarity, 1960; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.10 (1960: Aug. 29). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 17: UAW Solidarity, 1960; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.11 (1960: Sept. 12). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 18: UAW Solidarity, 1960; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.12 (1960: Sept. 26). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 19: UAW Solidarity, 1960; Publication (Box 137, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.13 (1960: Oct. 10). Eastern Edition.
- UAW Solidarity, 1961-1963 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: UAW Solidarity, 1961; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.2 (1961: Feb.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 2: UAW Solidarity, 1961; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.10 (1961: Oct.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 3: UAW Solidarity, 1961; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.4:no.12 (1961: Dec.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 4: UAW Solidarity, 1962; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.2 (1962: Feb.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 5: UAW Solidarity, 1962; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.3 (1962: Mar.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 6: UAW Solidarity, 1962; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.4 (1962: Apr.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 7: UAW Solidarity, 1962; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.5 (1962: May). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 8: UAW Solidarity, 1962; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.6 (1962: June). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 9: UAW Solidarity, 1962; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.7 (1962: July). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 10: UAW Solidarity, 1962; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.8 (1962: Aug.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 11: UAW Solidarity, 1962; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.9 (1962: Sept.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 12: UAW Solidarity, 1962; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.5:no.11 (1962: Nov.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 13: UAW Solidarity, 1963; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.1 (1963: Jan.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 14: UAW Solidarity, 1963; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.2 (1963: Feb.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 15: UAW Solidarity, 1963; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.3 (1963: Mar.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 16: UAW Solidarity, 1963; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.4 (1963: Apr.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 17: UAW Solidarity, 1963; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.5 (1963: May). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 18: UAW Solidarity, 1963; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.6 (1963: June). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 19: UAW Solidarity, 1963; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.7 (1963: July). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 20: UAW Solidarity, 1963; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.8 (1963: Aug.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 21: UAW Solidarity, 1963; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.9 (1963: Sept.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 22: UAW Solidarity, 1963; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.10 (1963: Oct.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 23: UAW Solidarity, 1963; Publication (Box 137, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.6:no.12 (1963: Dec.). Eastern Edition.
- UAW Solidarity, 1964-1965 (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: UAW Solidarity, 1964; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.7:no.1 (1964: Jan.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 2: UAW Solidarity, 1964; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.7:no.2 (1964: Feb.). Eastern Edition.
  - Item 3: UAW Solidarity, 1964; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.7:no.6 (1964: June)
  - Item 4: UAW Solidarity, 1964; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.7:no.7 (1964: July)
  - Item 5: UAW Solidarity, 1964; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.7:no.8 (1964: Aug.)
  - Item 6: UAW Solidarity, 1964; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.7:no.9 (1964: Sept.)
  - Item 7: UAW Solidarity, 1964; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.7:no.10 (1964: Oct.)
  - Item 8: UAW Solidarity, 1964; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.7:no.11 (1964: Nov.)
  - Item 9: UAW Solidarity, 1964; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.7:no.12 (1964: Dec.)
  - Item 10: UAW Solidarity, 1965; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1965: Jan.)
  - Item 11: UAW Solidarity, 1965; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.2 (1965: Feb.)
  - Item 12: UAW Solidarity, 1965; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.3 (1965: Mar.)
  - Item 13: UAW Solidarity, 1965; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.4 (1965: Apr.)
  - Item 14: UAW Solidarity, 1965; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.5 (1965: May)
  - Item 15: UAW Solidarity, 1965; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.6 (1965: June)
  - Item 16: UAW Solidarity, 1965; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.7 (1965: July)
  - Item 17: UAW Solidarity, 1965; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.8 (1965: Aug.)
  - Item 18: UAW Solidarity, 1965; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.9 (1965: Sept.)
  - Item 19: UAW Solidarity, 1965; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.8:no.10 (1965: Oct.)
  - Item 20: UAW Solidarity, 1965; Publication (Box 138, Folder 1)